Who's there?
Stop!
How dare you chase me alone?
Since you saw me,
I can't let you live.
Ah!
Oh no, I was too impulsive.
Uncle taught me this.
Spiritual power?
Isn't she a mortal?
It worked!
But the problem is,
I can't hold on much longer.
He was also injured by my spiritual power.
Uncle, listen to me.
Don't say anything.
Go back and rest first.
Ye Qifeng,
deal with that man yourself.
Yes.
Uncle,
you saw me use spiritual power,
didn't you?
Are you suspecting me too?
But I really don't remember anything,
and I have no intention of harming anyone.
If you still don't believe me,
it's okay.
I believe you.
I...
Uncle, what did you say?
I said,
I believe you.
Uncle.
Who is this?
You must be A'kong.
I am the healer of Yan Sect.
Everyone calls me Medical Maniac.
Let me take a look at you.
Then, sorry to trouble you.
What did he see in my body?
Is it good or bad?
Could I really be a
monster?
Girl, there's nothing seriously wrong
with your body.
It's just that
there's a very special power inside you.
It's extremely powerful,
but it seems to be wrapped by something
and cannot be released.
Power? But I can't feel it at all.
You lost your memory,
right?
This power seems to be sealed
along with your
memory.
Sect Leader, she is indeed not a mortal,
but she is definitely not
an ordinary demon either.
I have practiced medicine
for thousands of years
and have never seen her constitution.
The power in her body
carries an ancient aura.
If released,
I'm afraid the entire demon realm
will be shaken.
But right now, she's like a sealed bottle.
The bottle contains a tsunami,
but the bottle itself
is incredibly fragile.
What about her injuries?
It's fine.
They are all superficial wounds.
I'll prescribe some medicine.
She'll be fine after resting for two days.
Girl, come to
the Medicine Valley tomorrow.
I'll prepare a special medicine for you.
It might help relieve
your physical discomfort.
Thank you, Grandpa.
It's so comfortable here.
Madam,
Senior Medical Maniac is inside.
I will wait for you outside.
Don't call me Madam.
Just call me A'kong.
That's her.
the mortal of unknown origin
who seduced the Sect Leader.
I've heard the Sect Leader
let her stay in his room.
Even Commander Ye has started
calling her Madam.
How can a piece of trash
without any spiritual power deserve this?